

Ali Emami

Full Stack Developer

DoB: 2000-01-04
Marital Status: Single
Military Sarving: Educational

Military Service: Educational Exemption



aliemami.coder@gmail.com



(+98)9145805045



04134250616



No. 27, Golestan Ave, Andisheh City, Tabriz , East Azerbaijan, Iran

Summary

I am a web developer with 5+ years of experience in creating and maintaining web applications. I specialize in developing websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and other web development technologies. My experience includes developing responsive websites for a variety of clients, from small businesses to large corporations. I have a passion for creating user-friendly and visually appealing websites that are optimized for performance. I am also experienced in troubleshooting and debugging web applications to ensure they are running smoothly. In addition to my technical skills, I have excellent communication and problem-solving skills that allow me to work effectively with clients and colleagues.

Education

Bachelor of Software Engineer

Branch: Al Institute/University: Bonab Bonab , East Azerbaijan, Iran

GPA: 15

1397 - Present

Skills

C++	** *	Adobe Photoshop	** *
SEO SEO	***	PHP	****
Wordpress Programming	****	JQuery	****
Laravel	****	Bootstrap	****
Python	***	adobe xd	****
Java	***	Javascript	****
Vuejs	***	Git	****
React js	****	React Native	** *
Nodejs	***	Express js	** *
Rest api	****	Open Card	♦♦ ♦♦
Ant Design	AAAA	Next is	

Work Experience

PHP programmer

May 2018 - October 2018

Sabinserver Azarshahr, East Azerbaijan, Iran

IT manager

September 2020 - December 2020

Faraz Sanat Palize Tabriz, East Azerbaijan, Iran

Full Stack Developer

May 2021 - Present

Sakhtbazar Tabriz , East Azerbaijan, Iran

Full Stack Developer

Arongroups

Iran

June 2021 - Present

Language

English







Speaking



Listening Writing

60%

100%

Turkish







Speaking



Listening

Azerbaijani



Reading





Listening

Persian



Reading





Listening

Projects

Order registration system

September 2020

For: Bronze Castle

Order registration system designed with Laravel and Vue JS

Real estate online

For: Barish Vira

Online real estate system for registering real estate ads on the map designed with Laravel and Next js

Dedicated CRM system

February 2022

For: Sakhtbazar

Development a dedicated CRM system with personalization capabilities designed with Laravel and React js

Sakhtkar April 2022

For: Sakhtbazar

Advertisement and tender registration system in the field of construction designed with Laravel and Next js Link: https://sakhtkaar.ir

Sakhtbazar September 2022

For: Sakhtbazar

Advanced B2B system development with Laravel

Link: https://sakhtbazar.com

UI/UX design of job creation system

May 2022

For: Sakhtbazar

UI/UX design of market building system with Adobe XD tools

Aaron Group's anniversary landing

October 2022

For: Arongroups

Aaron Group's anniversary landing page design

Link: http://aron-anniversary.com/

Aron Charts trading platform

February 2022

For: Arongroups

The platform for analysis and review of digital currency charts and forex symbols and storage and retrieval of analyzes designed with Laravel and React js

Link: https://aroncharts.com/

Trading platform for football players

June 2022

For: Arongroups

The website for displaying information and valuing players and creating the possibility of analysis for trading designed with Laravel and React js

Link: https://aronfootball.com/

Honors

Winning the third place in the provincial stage of the ACM competition

October 2019

Winning the third place in the national stage of the ACM Hamedan competition

November 2019

Social Network

aliemami.py 🦪

aliemami_coder in ali-emami